https://www.rundles.co.uk/privacy-notice/

0
-
My Account
This privacy policy sets out how Rundles uses and protects any information that you give Rundles when you use this website. Rundles is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Rundles may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the list of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@rundles.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to New Bolingbroke, Boston, Lincolnshire, PE22 7LN.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Rundles.co.uk uses cookies. We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services.
Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user's experience more efficient.
The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission.
This site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.
Your consent applies to the following domains: www.rundles.co.uk
Your current state: Allow all cookies (Necessary, Preferences, Statistics, Marketing).
Change your consent  |  Withdraw your consent
Cookie declaration last updated on 28/10/2019 by Cookiebot:
Necessary (4)
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Name
Provider
Purpose
Expiry
Type
CookieConsent
rundles.co.uk
Stores the user's cookie consent state for the current domain
1 year
HTTP Cookie
external_no_cache
rundles.co.uk
Records whether caching of a page is allowed or not on the visitor's browser.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
frontend
rundles.co.uk
Stores a random ID which ensures that a user can be uniquely identified as a guest or logged-in user. Functions such as "Items last viewed" or retention of the logged-in state are connected with this cookie.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
frontend_cid
rundles.co.uk
Stores a random ID which ensures that a user can be uniquely identified as a guest or logged-in user on encrypted pages. Functions such as "Items last viewed" or retention of the logged-in state are connected with this cookie.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
Statistics (6)
Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Name
Provider
Purpose
Expiry
Type
_at.hist.#
rundles.co.uk
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to store the user's usage history of the AddThis sharing widget
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
_ga
rundles.co.uk
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 years
HTTP Cookie
_gat
rundles.co.uk
Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate
1 day
HTTP Cookie
_gid
rundles.co.uk
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
collect
google-analytics.com
Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.
Session
Pixel Tracker
wui
weborama.com
Contains an visitor ID - This is used to identify the visitor upon re-entry to the website.
3 months
HTTP Cookie
Marketing (55)
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
Name
Provider
Purpose
Expiry
Type
__atuvc
rundles.co.uk
Updates the counter of a website's social sharing features.
13 months
HTTP Cookie
__atuvs
rundles.co.uk
Ensures that the updated counter is displayed to the user if a page is shared with the social sharing service, AddThis.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
_at.cww
rundles.co.uk
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
_tmid
tubemogul.com
Registers a unique ID that identifies the user's device upon return visits. The ID is used to target ads in video clips.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
AFFICHE_W
weborama.fr
Used by the advertising platform Weborama to determine the visitor's interests based on pages visits, content clicked and other actions on the website.
3 months
HTTP Cookie
at-lojson-cache-#
rundles.co.uk
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
at-rand
rundles.co.uk
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
B
yahoo.com
Collects anonymous data related to the user's website visits, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded. The registered data is used to categorise the users' interest and demographical profiles with the purpose of customising the website content depending on the visitor.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
bkdc
bluekai.com
Registers anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
bkpa
bluekai.com
Used to present the visitor with relevant content and advertisement - The service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitate real-time bidding for advertisers.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
bku
bluekai.com
Registers anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
bt2
addthis.com
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to keep a record of parts of the site that has been visited in order to recommend other parts of the site
255 days
HTTP Cookie
demdex
demdex.net
Via a unique ID that is used for semantic content analysis, the user's navigation on the website is registered and linked to offline data from surveys and similar registrations to display targeted ads.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
di2
addthis.com
Pending
1 year
HTTP Cookie
dpm
demdex.net
Sets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
eud
rfihub.com
Registers anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
GPS
youtube.com
Registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
IDE
doubleclick.net
Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.
2 years
HTTP Cookie
loc
addthis.com
Geolocation, which is used to help providers determine how users who share information with each other are geographically located (state level).
13 months
HTTP Cookie
mus
addthis.com
Pending
1 year
HTTP Cookie
mv3
cardlytics.com
Pending
179 days
HTTP Cookie
na_id
addthis.com
Used to recognize the visitor upon re-entry. This allows the website to register the visitor’s behaviour and facilitate the social sharing function provided by Addthis.com.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
ouid
addthis.com
Sets an ID-string for the specific visitor. This is used to recognize the visitor upon re-entry. This allows the website to register the visitor’s behaviour and facilitate the social media sharing function provided by Addthis.com.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
pt
ispot.tv
Pending
2 years
HTTP Cookie
rc::c
google.com
Used in context with video-advertisement. The cookie limits the number of times a visitor is shown the same advertisement-content. The cookie is also used to ensure relevance of the video-advertisement to the specific visitor.
Session
HTML Local Storage
rud
rfihub.com
Registers anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
ruds
rfihub.com
Registers anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network.
Session
HTTP Cookie
ssi
sitescout.com
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
svResp
survata.com
Pending
6 months
HTTP Cookie
sync-his
tidaltv.com
Sets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
TapAd_DID
tapad.com
Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc.) is used by a user.
2 months
HTTP Cookie
TapAd_TS
tapad.com
Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc.) is used by a user.
2 months
HTTP Cookie
TDCPM
adsrvr.org
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
TDID
adsrvr.org
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
test_cookie
doubleclick.net
Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies.
1 day
HTTP Cookie
tidal_ttid
tidaltv.com
Registers the ads provided by Videology that the user has seen and/or clicked. Used to generate a demographic profile of the user.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
uid [x2]
addthis.com
turn.com
Creates a unique, machine-generated user ID. AddThis, which is owned by Clearspring Technologies, uses the user ID to make it possible for the user to share content across social networks and provide detailed statistics to various providers.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
um
addthis.com
Registers the user's sharing of content via social media.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
uuid
mathtag.com
Collects data on the user's visits to the website, such as what pages have been loaded. The registered data is used for targeted ads.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
uuid2
adnxs.com
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
3 months
HTTP Cookie
uuidc
mathtag.com
Collects data on the user's visits to the website, such as what pages have been loaded. The registered data is used for targeted ads.
1 year
HTTP Cookie
uvc
addthis.com
Detects how often the social sharing service, AddThis, encounters the same user.
13 months
HTTP Cookie
vc
addthis.com
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis
1 year
HTTP Cookie
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
youtube.com
Tries to estimate the users' bandwidth on pages with integrated YouTube videos.
179 days
HTTP Cookie
wam-sync
weborama.com
Used to track visitors on multiple websites, in order to present relevant advertisement based on the visitor's preferences.
6 days
HTTP Cookie
wfivefivec
w55c.net
Collects data on the user's visits to the website, such as what pages have been loaded. The registered data is used for targeted ads.
13 months
HTTP Cookie
xtc
addthis.com
Registers the user's sharing of content via social media.
13 months
HTTP Cookie
YSC
youtube.com
Registers a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
Session
HTTP Cookie
yt-remote-cast-installed
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML Local Storage
yt-remote-connected-devices
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
yt-remote-device-id
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Persistent
HTML Local Storage
yt-remote-fast-check-period
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML Local Storage
yt-remote-session-app
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML Local Storage
yt-remote-session-name
youtube.com
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML Local Storage
Your rights
In this Section, we have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
Your principal rights under data protection law are:
(a) the right to access;
(b) the right to rectification;
(c) the right to erasure;
(d) the right to restrict processing;
(e) the right to object to processing;
(f) the right to data portability;
(g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
(h) the right to withdraw consent.
Deleting your account
You can delete all the details we hold on our system together with your account with us and any service you may have signed up for such as our newsletter. Your orders will be anonymized. Please note that once your account is deleted you will not be able to access any previous orders or communications, they will all be permanently deleted.
Click here to go to your account page where you will see 'Delete My Account' in the left-hand menu.
Privacy policy – The Finer Details GDPR - Last updated 21/03/2018
1. Introduction
1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors.
1.2 This policy applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to the personal data of our website visitors and service users; in other words, where we determine the purposes and means of the processing of that personal data.
1.3 We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website. OR By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
1.4 Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications and limit the publication of your information. You can access the privacy controls when you first visit our website
1.5 In this policy, "we", "us" and "our" refer to J H Rundle Ltd.[ For more information about us, see Section 13.]
2. Credit
2.1 This document was created using a template from SEQ Legal
3. How we use your personal data
3.1 In this Section 3 we have set out:
(a) the general categories of personal data that we may process;
(b) [in the case of personal data that we did not obtain directly from you, the source and specific categories of that data];
(c) the purposes for which we may process personal data; and
(d) the legal bases of the processing.
3.2 We may process data about your use of our website and services ("usage data"). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services.
3.3 We may process your account data ("account data").[ The account data may include your name and email address. The source of the account data is you or your employer. The account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business OR the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
3.4  We may process your information included in your personal profile on our website ("profile data"). The profile data may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details and employment details. The profile data may be processed for the purposes of enabling and monitoring your use of our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business OR the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at you request, to enter into such a contract.
3.5 We may process your personal data that are provided in the course of the use of our services ("service data"). The service data may include include your name and email address. The source of the service data is you or your employer. The service data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business OR the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
3.6 We may process information that you post for publication on our website or through our services ("publication data"). The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business OR [the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
3.7 We may process information contained in any enquiry you submit to us regarding goods and/or services ("enquiry data"). The enquiry data may be processed for the purposes of offering, marketing and selling relevant goods and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
3.8 We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website ("transaction data").The transaction data may include your contact details, your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed [for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate interests, namely [our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.
3.9 We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters ("notification data"). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
3.10 We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us ("correspondence data"). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.
3.11 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.
3.12 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.
3.13 In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this Section 3, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary[ for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
3.14 Please do not supply any other person's personal data to us, unless we prompt you to do so.
4. Providing your personal data to others
4.1 We may disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the legal bases, set out in this policy.
4.2 We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
4.3 We may disclose your personal data to our suppliers or subcontractors identified at www.rundles.co.uk insofar as reasonably necessary for fulfilling orders and services.
4.4 Financial transactions relating to our website and services are handled by our payment services providers, Paypal and Stripe Inc.. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers' privacy policies and practices at https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full  and  https://stripe.com/gb/privacy.
4.5 We may disclose your enquiry data to one or more of those selected third party suppliers of goods and services identified on our website for the purpose of enabling them to contact you so that they can offer, market and sell to you relevant goods and/or services. Each such third party will act as a data controller in relation to the enquiry data that we supply to it; and upon contacting you, each such third party will supply to you a copy of its own privacy policy, which will govern that third party's use of your personal data.
4.6 In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section 4, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
5. International transfers of your personal data
5.1 J H Rundle Ltd are only based in the United Kingdom and only use servers for our website based in the United Kingdom.
6. Retaining and deleting personal data
6.1 This Section 6 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.
6.2 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
6.3 We will retain your personal data as follows:
(a) Your personal information will be retained for a period of time following your order date/account creation through our website, and for a maximum period until deletion of your account.
6.5 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 6, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
7. Amendments
7.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.
7.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.
7.3 We may notify you of changes to this policy by email or through the private messaging system on our website.
8. Your rights
8.1 You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you; provision of such information will be subject to:
(a)  the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).
8.2 We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.
8.3 You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes.
8.4 In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.
OR
8. Your rights
8.1 In this Section 8, we have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
8.2 Your principal rights under data protection law are:
(a) the right to access;
(b) the right to rectification;
(c) the right to erasure;
(d) the right to restrict processing;
(e) the right to object to processing;
(f) the right to data portability;
(g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
(h) the right to withdraw consent.
8.3 You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee. You can access your personal data by visiting https://www.rundles.co.uk/my-account/ when logged into our website.
8.4 You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
8.5 In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: [the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
8.6 In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.
8.7 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
8.8 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.
8.9 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.
8.10 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:
(a) consent; or
(b) that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract,
and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.
8.11 If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.
8.12 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
8.13 You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us, in addition to the other methods specified in this Section 8.
9. About cookies
9.1 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
9.2 Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
9.3 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.
11. Cookies used by our service providers
11.1 Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.
11.2 We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
12. Managing cookies
12.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:
(a)  https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);
(b) https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox);
(c) http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);
(d) https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);
(e) https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and
(f) https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge).
12.2 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
12.3 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.
13. Our details
13.1 This website is owned and operated by John H Rundle Ltd.
13.2 We are registered in [England and Wales] under registration number 841783, and our registered office is at Main Road, New Bolingbroke, Boston, Lincolnshire, PE22 7LN
13.3 Our principal place of business is at Main Road, New Bolingbroke, Boston, Lincolnshire, PE22 7LN.
13.4 You can contact us:
(a) by post, to the postal address given above;
(b) using our website contact form;
(c) by telephone, 01205 480431 during our office hours
(d) by email, sales@rundles.co.uk
14. Data protection officer
14.1 Our data protection officer's for the website contact details are: tony@rundles.co.uk.
